export default data = [
  {
      question: "The sentence written on the board is ______ .  It has more than one meaning",
      options: ["ambiguous","convincing","elegant","universal"],
      correct_option: "ambiguous"
  },
  {
      question: "Because Mr. Wang ______ changes his mind, it’s very difficult to predict what he will do next",
      options: ["additionally","honorably","probably","constantly"],
      correct_option: "constantly"
  },
  {
      question: "Many students find it hard to focus on their studies when holidays are ______",
      options: ["approaching","dismissing","expanding","presenting"],
      correct_option: "approaching"
  },
  {
      question: "During the process of evolution, man has shown remarkable ability to ______ to the environment",
      options: ["adorn","adopt","adore","adapt"],
      correct_option: "adapt"
  },
  {
      question: "The young scientist showed great ______ for his success.  He said that it was as much the result of good luck as his own talent",
      options: ["dignity","modesty","intensity","identity"],
      correct_option: "modesty"
  },
  {
      question: "Ladies and gentlemen, it is my ______ to speak to you all on this special occasion",
      options: ["company","dignity","privilege","eloquence"],
      correct_option: "privilege"
  },
  {
      question: "It was a great ______ for his family that he had survived the cold weather in the mountain",
      options: ["moral","promise","relief","success"],
      correct_option: "relief"
  },
  {
      question: "The landslide after the typhoon signals that environmental protection ______ our attention",
      options: ["accuses","stretches","obtains","deserves"],
      correct_option: "deserves"
  },
  {
      question: "Cars in the future will be characterized by their ______ use of gasoline",
      options: ["affective","efficient","immediate","traditional"],
      correct_option: "efficient"
  },
  {
      question: "Physically, Peter is well-built, yet ______ , he is very weak and dependent",
      options: ["passionately","relentlessly","emotionally","heartily"],
      correct_option: "emotionally"
  },
  {
      question: "Kevin is ______ , because he broke the living room window this afternoon",
      options: ["in control","in trouble","in turn","in vain"],
      correct_option: "in trouble"
  },
  {
      question: "If all the manufacturers can ______ during this financial crisis, the economy may get better next quarter",
      options: ["call up","give in","hang on","let in"],
      correct_option: "hang on"
  },
  {
      question: "Don’t worry about your grades. Just concentrate on your studies.  Hard work often ______ the best in you",
      options: ["brings out","gives away","looks over","splits off"],
      correct_option: "brings out"
  },
  {
      question: "The young man owes his success to many people, his parents ______",
      options: ["after all","by chance","on purpose","in particular"],
      correct_option: "in particular"
  },
  {
      question: "He was late for the meeting ______ the heavy rain",
      options: ["as a result of","in accordance with","in spite of","apart from"],
      correct_option: "as a result of"
  },
]
